Blogs so what is today's blog thumbnail you must have come to
know so today has been a
very interesting day filled with many experiences
because today's blog is
very special for me because today it has been
one year of Bhumi so I am very happy so there is
something else important in today's blog
which I will tell you later
in the video so without any reason let me
start the video this is
our Bhumi so happy birthday you and me so
today Jhoomi's one year shop is complete are you seeing in
what condition it is still and I wanted to
tell you one thing that the next day before I went to college
my rear tyre was
broken so I removed it completely so I will tell you
all that
if you do not fix the tyre then here
before the start of this video I will show you
how much the vehicle has run till now so after one year
when it is completing one year so I am
showing you here so here you are seeing it it has turned on so Bhumi is
also there together
I have just only  I have just driven ₹5000 for 87 km, so that is why it
is still brand new
and if we talk about it, I did
not face any major problem with the bike, you must have
seen my video in which I got the lever
changed, got the brakes changed, got the
indicator changed, now there was no
major problem with the bike,
so you guys are seeing it and my
engine exhauster, I can say, the
exhauster is fading a bit but it is okay,
this happens with bikes, so you are
seeing it now, it is still in mint condition,
my car has run just 5000 and you can see
how good it looks from the front,
still let's go, I have to get it refilled, there is
no petrol in it right now, so the
gas is high here right now, so when the petrol gets full,
then I can show it and right now
I can show you guys in the indicator,
what is it showing in the indication right now, right now
you guys are seeing here that it is
showing low here also, so when the fuel
level is low, then I can see it, right now it is low in it  It is
also feeling that there is a little bit of air left
in the tyres right now, so when that is done, I will check that too.
I have just
refuelled it, I have also filled 150 petrol
and now I will turn it on and
see, it is done, so now I will go to the settings and
reset it again so that I can
know what is the average mileage we are giving,
but let me show you that
last time I drove it, it is showing with the mileage,
so you can see that the average is still showing 51,
so now I will reset it, when it is done, when
I drive it, then I will give you an overview, so it has been
decided, okay, I will take it a
little further, where I will get the
tyres filled, you can
see, it is still running well, it is good
from the front as well and brother,
thank you for all the love here for so long, sir, can you see,
brother, it is still running the same way,
then I will check it
[Music]
I have got both the refuelling and tyre pressure done
and now the car is going to run like a machine,
so whatever my  As I
told you, it has been a year, so today I have to
renew my bumper to bumper insurance, so
I am going to TVS right now, sir, I will
tell you the further process
because when you people
buy a car, the bumper to bumper insurance that
comes with you is for one year, so today it will
expire, before that I will have to go
there and renew it, otherwise if by
chance in future if the car meets with an
accident,
I will have to pay the entire amount, that is why I am going right now,
sir, I will go to TVS, after that I will
continue the video, the gas is ready and it is
ready in our room too, so you go, sir, I will go to TVS, I will continue the
video, I have brought it with me,
sir, I will go to TVS, I will
show you the process that happens inside,
so I am going inside on my own, I will
tell you the process that happens, how to get the
insurance renewed, my insurance is
complete, so Amit Bhaiya got my
insurance done, so I got it done in cash, it was
not possible to do cashless because the
process for that  Which has changed now,
so for that Bhaiya said that now
everything is connected with Digilocker, so
you will have to give the password of Digilocker as well, only then
your cashless process will be done,
otherwise it does not happen
and I have got it done cashless only, so here
you people are seeing that above, I have got it done through New
India only, so I have got the
casting done for
1450, I have got it done in cash, so
if my car meets with an accident now, then
I will get 80% because after one year the
value of the car decreases, so you
people should keep this in mind, so if you want to get insurance done, then if you get it done
a day before or
later, then you people will have to pay more than this,
short 150, whatever it is
and I forgot to say one thing, I am talking about cashless,
cashless is such a thing which you
people should know, so cashless will happen only
through the company, that is, the showroom which belongs to the company, so the
benefit you get in cashless is that if
your car meets with an accident, then if  When
you go to buy a car, you wo
n't have to pay any money or do anything.
You just sign and go and take the car.
What happens in cashless, the company does the processing and
they will send the money to your account.
After that, when you go to take the car,
this cashless business is from the showroom. The
showroom, what do you
call it? There will be no middle man here. The
showroom's connection with the company will handle it.
Secondly, you will go in the beginning and you
cannot do it cashless.
You will have to come to the showroom and get it done where you
buy everything or where you renew your insurance. So,
always remember this.
As I was telling you,
today is the completion of one year of Bhoomi,
so we have also done a little washing,
but you won't know on the video. So, I will get
it washed today
because I had left it at
home for a long time. I won't wash it today, but if it's
her birthday or first anniversary,
I will talk to her today for that and I will
show you what happens after that.
[Music]
In service, Sharma ji is there.  You are watching,
Bhoomi is standing, so I will
send her for watching now, when the washing is done and she
comes out after washing, then I
will tell you, there is a lot of rush here, so you are
also hearing it or not, I don't know, but it is too much
here
[Music]
Iron Maa,
take it more please
[Music]
What is it, I like you, remember, but you give me our everything
Complete, you guys are watching, you are looking completely
new, so I have just renewed its insurance, as
I told you,
1450, so I am taking it now, I am
not going home, I am going, so
wherever I go, I will see you guys, then you
guys will come to know what I am going to get done in the next step
up, the
Balaji stickering, where I had got
Atul Box written earlier, so here today I am
giving a gift, here I am loving it
[Music] I was
thinking about it for a long time, so you are watching here,
I got its batting done, it is
my birthday date
[Prashansa]
So let's go now, some public  There's a
fair going on here to watch a movie, so
[Music]
As I was saying, I was coming to another place, so
after this sticking, I came
here to get the pollution checked,
you guys can see here, so when your vehicle completes
one year, you guys have to get the
pollution checked once, as it was
written in our manual that for one year after
purchase, you do
n't have to check any policy, but
after one year, you have to come here and get the
production checked once, so I got it done, it cost
me 100 rupees, so
you guys can also get it done, if
you complete one year in the rudder, then by doing this
you can deduct the pollution, so that you
guys can go back to finding it later, it's done
and I got a small gift, if anyone is there, you
can see this, I got the pollution done for
my bike, which I got done after one year, so
you guys should also get it done,
otherwise I will definitely get a fine, so you guys should also get it done, so I
'm leaving now, I'll
see whatever is there
[Music]  I had to
tell you something first, so let's
talk about it in the big, we all
start, so
you guys also take care
[Sangeet]
So you guys keep giving me this love and support
and there is something else interesting too, now let me
tell you, so how is Bhumi doing, I mean, how is she doing,
or tell me by commenting, if you have any other
questions, you guys
could have
commented and the videos will keep coming, but keep
supporting and loving, going
forward
[Sangeet]
So, everyone, I was telling you what the surprise is, so here is the
surprise, Bhumi,
on the occasion of her first anniversary, as we say,
so Mummy is cutting the cake and she is
here, so I am very happy that we were able to do this today, so come on
Mummy, quickly cut the cake, so
this is
Happy Birthday to you
[Sangeet] No
problem,
you are watching
[Sangeet]
So because of this, the full video is complete and
what can I say, she is looking so cute, you
guys are watching,
you guys are watching, she is so happy, I mean, there are
many people who do not celebrate their
bike's birthday at all, but for me, today
her birthday was very special, so it would have been evening, that's
why  I thought no let's complete the video now
so I got it
and celebrated so happy birthday to you me
home me so there will be more interesting videos so see you on the
next block
supporting stage now guys everyone and soon a
new block is coming so see you on the next block
one is already on so see you on
someone right now
[Music]